(Leonard:)It's from Game of Thrones.
(Leonard:)- What do you think?
- I don't know.
(Sheldon:)If we're going to start
a fantasy sword collection...
And l've long thought we should.
(Sheldon:)...is this really the sword to start with?
(Leonard:)What did you have in mind?
(Sheldon:)Well, off the top of my head,
I'd have to go with Excalibur.
(Sheldon:)It gives you the right to rule England.
(Leonard:)It would be a replica of a movie prop.
(Sheldon:)Fair enough.
It would give you the right
to rule a replica of England.
(Leonard:)Well, they don't have an Excalibur here,
so, what do you want to do?
Ugh, tough decision.
(Sheldon:)There's no weaponry
from Lord of the Rings...
(Sheldon:)...forged in a Chinese sweatshop?
Mm-hm, just Bilbo Baggins'
sword over there.
(Sheldon:)Two grown men with a hobbit's dagger,
wouldn't we look silly?
(Sheldon:)- Okay, let's go for it.
Heh.